https://www.tribeazure.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.TribeAzure.com
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact our customer service department by email at service@tribeazure.com. TRIBE AZURE wholeheartedly respects your privacy and will NEVER rent or sell your personal information to any third party. When you visit www.TribeAzure.com, we collect some basic information in order to better serve your experience navigating the website. The information collected by Tribe Azure includes products purchased, feedback from visitors, location data, logs and other communication data, information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type. This information is then aggregated with other pieces of information to improve our site and make your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible.
If you purchase an item online from Tribe Azure, interact with www.TribeAzure.com by submitting feedback, or opt to receive the Tribe Azure newsletter, you provide us with personally identifiable information including your first and last name, and email addresses. Your Credit Card payment is managed by Pay Pal, and is not visible or collected by Tribe Azure.
The information you provide to Tribe Azure will be used to process your order. You will only be contacted by Tribe Azure if you place an order or if there is a problem with your order. By placing an order you will automatically receive the Tribe Azure Newsletter by email, but you can always change your email preferences if you wish to be removed from our list by simply emailing us at service@TribeAzure.com.
Tribe Azure collects non-personal information about our website traffic and usage patterns from technology such as Cookies. We use cookies to keep track of the items that you have placed in your shopping cart, and to enhance your experience on www.TribeAzure.com. If your cookies are turned off, you will not be able to shop online with Tribe Azure. However, you may still place your order by telephone. We recommend that you turn your cookies on while shopping at Tribe Azure, as this will allow for a much more enjoyable and worry-free shopping experience.
Tribe Azure does not knowingly collect any personal information from children.
